ACTWU's Secretary-Treasurer's Office Records 5619/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU's Secretary-Treasurer's Office Records
1928-1997
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America
Jacob Potofsky
Frank Rosenblum
Joseph Schlossberg
Jacob Sheinkman
5619/018
136 cubic feet
136 linear feet
Correspondence, reports, publications.
This collection consists of correspondence, reports, and files from the Secretary-Treasurer's Office of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America and the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union. During the time period of these records, this office was held by Joseph Schlossberg, Jacob Potofsky, Frank Rosenblum, and Jacob Sheinkman.
6832647
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
June 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 2011
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related collections: 5619: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America 5619/004: ACTWU's Jacob Sheinkman Records from the Sectretary-Treasurer's and President's Offices 5619/004 mf: ACTWU's Microfiche Collection of Jacob Sheinkman's Speeches 5619/029: ACTWU's Vice-President's Office Records And all other 5619 collections.
Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing trade -- New York (State); Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives; Schlossberg, Joseph, 1875-1971.; Potofsky, Jacob S. (Jacob Samuel), 1894-1979; Rosenblum, Frank, 1888-1973; Sheinkman, Jacob, 1926-2004
6832647
- Task Force on the Impact of National Health Insurance [folder 1 of 4], 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Task Force on the Impact of National Health Insurance [folder 2 of 4], 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Task Force on the Impact of National Health Insurance [Folder 3 of 4], 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Task Force on the Impact of National Health Insurance [Folder 4 of 4], 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Committee on Labor Hearings, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- NRA Labor Program, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Fair Labor Standards Act Statements, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Fair Labor Standards Act Certificates, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Fair Labor Standards Act Wage Agreements. [Folder 1 of 2], 1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Fair Labor Standards Act Wage Agreements. [Folder 2 of 2], 1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Hosiery Industry, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Misc. Industries, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Knitted Wear Industry, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Textile Industry, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Neckwear Industry, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry. [Folder 1 of 2], 1939 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry. [Folder 2 of 2], 1939 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- US Department of Labor: Wage and Hour Division Report, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Committee on the Revision of Fair Labor Standards Act Report, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Proposed Amendments, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Statements, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Preliminary Analysis, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Proposed Revision Research, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Surveys, 1942-1945 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Annual Reports, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Proposed Amendments, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Glove Industry Notes, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry Reports, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry Statements, 1951-1954 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry Statements, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Amendments and Statements. [Folder 1 of 2], 1960 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Amendments and Statements. [Folder 2 of 2], 1960 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Notes. [Folder 1 of 2], 1959 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Notes. [Folder 2 of 2], 1959 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Reports, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Statements, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Wage Provisions, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry. [Folder 1 of 2], 1941 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry. [Folder 2 of 2], 1941 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Textile Industry, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Knitted Wear Industry, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Sheltered Workshops, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Learners General, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry Reports, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Glove Industry, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Amendments. [Folder 1 of 2], 1955 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Amendments. [Folder 2 of 2], 1955 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Reports and Statements, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Glove Industry Hearings, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Statements and Testimony, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Employment of Learners, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Knitted Wear Industry, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Glove Industry Reports, 1953-1955 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Glove Industry Learners, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Learners General Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Learners General Reports, 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry Statements, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Regulations, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Bulletins, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Earnings Reports, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Comments, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Clippings, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Statements, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Legislative Bill Proposals, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Comments and Amendments, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry Revisions, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry Statistics, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry Research Files, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Apparel Industry Statistics, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Learners- Apparel Industry, 1964-1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Fair Labor Standards Act- General Research Files, 1961-1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Fair Labor Standards Act:Learners- Knitted Wear Industry, 1956-1961 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Learners- Retail Trade Statements, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Misc. Industries Statements, 1961-1965 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Employment Extension Proposals, 1962-1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Earnings Reports and Proposals, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Minimum Wage Discussions, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Minimum Wage Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Work Experience and Career Exploration Program Notes, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Apparel Industries, 1957-1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence:El Caso del Puerto Rico, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  Spanish
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Research Files, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Research Files, 1940-1952 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Puerto Rico: Economic Conditions Reports. [Folder 1 of 3], 1957-1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Puerto Rico: Economic Conditions Reports. [Folder 2 of 3], 1957-1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Puerto Rico: Economic Conditions Reports. [Folder 3 of 3], 1957-1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Minimum Wage Regulations and Procedures, 1959-1975 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Minimum Wages Under Commonwealth Law, 1955-1961 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Minimum Wages Under the Fair Labor Standards Act, 1956-1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Special Industry Committees, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Minimum Wage Reports, 1959-1962 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Shipment Records, 1954-1956 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Special Industry Committee No. 2, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Special Industry Committee, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Special Industry Committee: Hearing Materials, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Special Industry Committee No. 38-A, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Special Industry Committee No. 53, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Sweater and Knit Swimwear Committee, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Children's Dress Products Industry, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Textile Industry Committee, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Hosiery Industry Committee, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Review Committee Reports, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Mens Clothing Industry, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Leather Goods Industry, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Taxation Reports, 1957-1974 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Textile Industry Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Transportation Reports, 1955-1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Underwear Industry Reports, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Unionization Reports, 1957-1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Wage Reports, 1955-1961 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Gloves and Mittens Industry, 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Apparel Industry Minimum Wage Committee, 1959-1963 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Leather Industry Minimum Wage Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Wage Acts and Amendments, 1955-1962 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Industrialization Reports, 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Migration Reports, 1956-1964 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Labor and Education Committee, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Industrial Reports, 1958-1962 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Industrial Relations, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Walsh-Healey Act: Outerwear Industry, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Walsh-Healey Act: Gloves Industry, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Walsh-Healey Act: Cotton Garment Industry, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Walsh-Healey Act: Rainwear Industry, 1950-1956 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Walsh-Healey Act: Textile Industry, 1956-1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Walsh-Healey Act: Underwear Industry, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Walsh-Healey Act: Neckwear Industry, 1951-1954 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Walsh-Healey Act: Parachute Industry, 1952-1954 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Walsh-Healey Act: Amendments, 1950-1964 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Walsh-Healey Act: Statements, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Walsh-Healey Act: Reports Walsh-Healey Act: Reports, 1953-1962 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Walsh-Healey Act: Statements, 1940-1949 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Walsh-Healey Act: Statements, 1936-1938 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Walsh-Healey Act: Child Labor Reports, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Amendments in Puerto Rico, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Minimum Wage Statements, 1954-1976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Puerto Rico Correspondence: Minimum Wage Determination, 1949-1951 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Laundry, Cleaning and Dyeing Industry: Economic Conditions Reports, 1950-1961 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Laundry, Cleaning and Dyeing Industry: Financial Data, 1955-1960 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Laundry, Cleaning and Dyeing Industry: Fringe Benefits Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Laundry, Cleaning and Dyeing Industry: General Documents, 1940-1957 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Laundry, Cleaning and Dyeing Industry: Minimum Wage Legislation, 1960-1975 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Laundry, Cleaning and Dyeing Industry: Technology Reports, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Laundry, Cleaning and Dyeing Industry: Training Articles, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Laundry, Cleaning and Dyeing Industry: Wage Reports in the District of Columbia, 1943-1946 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Laundry, Cleaning and Dyeing Industry: District of Columbia Minimum Wage Board, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Laundry, Cleaning and Dyeing Industry: New Jersey Wage Reports, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Laundry, Cleaning and Dyeing Industry: New York Wage Reports, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Violations, 1937-1960 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Fair Labor Standards Act: Violation Evidence, 1932-1937 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Taft-Hartley Act: Reports and Statements, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Textile Merger Background, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Textile Merger Constitution and Formal Documents, 1972-1975 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America:Textile Merger Department Operations, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Textile Merger Draft of Documents, 1969-1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Textile Merger Finance Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Textile Merger Finance and Staff Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Textile Merger Messages, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Textile Merger Litigation, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Textile Merger Staff and Structure Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Textile Merger Structure and Operation Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Textile Workers Union: General Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Textile Merger Working File, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Textile Merger Agreement, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Election Notices, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America: Merger File Extra Copies, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- FARAH: Activity Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- FARAH: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America Position and Policy Statements, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- FARAH: Belgium Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  French
- FARAH: Belgium Reports, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- FARAH: Boycott Materials, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- FARAH: Clergy Relations, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- FARAH: Clergy Statements, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- FARAH: Company Employee Benefits, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- FARAH: Contribution and Co-Operation, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- FARAH: Contributions, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- FARAH: Contributions and Distribution of Holiday Fund, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- FARAH: Special Collections, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- FARAH: Demonstrations; Picketing Records, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- FARAH: Elections, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- FARAH: Expense Reports, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- FARAH: Far East Limited, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- FARAH: Film, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- FARAH: Financial and Business Data, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- FARAH: Newsletters, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- FARAH: Legal Documents, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- FARAH: National Labor Relations Board, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- FARAH: Organization Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- FARAH: Personnel Assignments, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- FARAH: Progress Reports, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- FARAH: Progress Reports, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- FARAH: Publications; Viva La Huelga, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- FARAH: Public Relations, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- FARAH: Strike Bulletins, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- FARAH: Retailers Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- FARAH: List of Retailers, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- FARAH: Citizens Committee for Justice Progress Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- FARAH: Salesmen Reports, 1968-1974 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- FARAH: Scandinavia Correspondence, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- FARAH: Norwegian Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  Norwegian
- FARAH: Strike Benefit Reports, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- FARAH: Strike Fund Assessments, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- FARAH: Individual Striker Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- FARAH: Travel Arrangements and Itinerary, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- FARAH: Union Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- FARAH: Annual Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Wolf and Company: Import Summary Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Atlantic Mills: Shreveport Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Spartan-Atlantic Negotiation, 1966-1972 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Atlantic Mills: St. Louis Statements, 1963-1967 (Box 14, Folder 4)